## **Bradon Ladd**

201 SW.  $1^{\text{st}}$  St. (apt. 428), College Place, WA, 99324

Cell: (785)-259-0652

Email: bradon.ladd@wallawalla.edu

## Summary

Service-minded, user focused individual with 4 years of personal technology experience across a wide variety of platforms including but not limited to: Cisco's PacketTracer, UNIX Systems, and personal networking devices. Various training in computer building, networking, and programming.

## **Skills and Expertise**

#### Service skills

- Self-motivated
- Good communicator
- Time manager
- Adaptable
- Team-oriented

## **Languages Used**

- Python
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- PHP/SQL
- C++/Java

## **Previous Work Experience**

Advertising and Promotional Graphic Designer: November 2018-Current EZ Mart – LaCrosse, KS - (785)-222-3443

- Work closely with superiors on designing eye-catching and informational promotional material for Walla Walla University campus events.
- Utilize cloud storage for easy transfer of files between myself and superior
- Routinely use and am comfortable with the entire Adobe Suite
- Work independently and keep a self-governed schedule to work on projects

<u>Convenience Store Clerk:</u> August 2017 – December 2017 EZ Mart – LaCrosse, KS - (785)-222-3443

- Kept store routinely clean and presentable
- Assisted diesel truckers with their transactions, hand-writing as many as 20 receipts per shift
- Processed over \$1,500 worth of cash, credit/debit card, and check transactions every shift
- Reconciled inventory with delivery invoices with a team on weekly truck deliveries
- Worked with school bus and government vehicle drivers to process their transactions on a separate charging system

Other Positions Held: Dietary Aide (June 2016 – September 2016, July 2017 - January 2018)

Kitchen Staff (January 2016 – July 2016)

Custodial (March 2017-September 2018)

#### Education

Upper Columbia Academy	High School Diploma
• •	•
Walla Walla University	Current, Computer Science and Graphic Design

# **Bradon Ladd**

## **REFERENCES**

Brenda Walsh, CEO of Rush County Memorial Hospital

Phone: (785)-222-2545

April Reed, Dietary Manager of Rush County Memorial Hospital

Phone: (785)-279-0164

Lori Milke, Owner of EZ Mart Convenience Stores

Phone: (785)-623-1632